Stonehenge Apocalypse is a science fiction, action, tv
movie film directed by Paul Ziller.
When a group of archaeologists dig up a human skeleton near Stonehenge, an
ancient piece of machinery hidden beneath the bedrock is discovered.
Not knowing what it could be, the workers accidentally trigger the mechanism and
start a chain of events that may very well end the world as we know it
Jacob Glaser, played by Misha Collins.
Dr. Kaycee Leeds, played by Torri Higginson.
Dr. John Trousdale, played by Peter Wingfield.
Joseph Leshem, played by Hill Harper.
David, played by David James Lewis.
Marla, played by Tina Milo Milivojevic.
Stonehenge Apocalypse is a 2010 Canadian made-for-TV science fiction film
starring Misha Collins, Torri Higginson and Peter Wingfield.
The movie follows a series of deaths, natural disasters, and strange energy
readings that seem to be mysteriously connected to Stonehenge.
The tone is thought_provoking.